I'm a visual artist and illustrator.
私はヴィジュアルアーティストと、イラストレーターをしているわ
Yeah, I produce illustrations that is formed from my imagination
私の描くイラストは、とりまく環境からの影響と、
as well as being influenced by sort of my environment.
私自身のイマジネーションで作られている
I guess my work's subject matter tends to be sort of a response to my environment
作品の主題は私を取り巻いている環境への 返答になっているような傾向があると思う
my own personal sort of reactions to the things that happen to me.
身の回りで起こることへの私自身の個人的な反応というか
And it's not just about the image that I'm creating but often it's
単に私が創り出しているイメージの事 だけではなく、ほとんどは
experimentation with line and how line can form the image
線の扱いや、その線でどうイメージをつくるかに 関しての実験なの
That has extended out into like my sort of stop motion mural work
それは拡張されて、ストップモーションの壁画の 作品とかにも入り込んでいる
In the sense that I experiment with line in story of sight-specific environments
場所性に則して、描画の実験をするという事で言えば
and then often re-animate them and project them back into the spaces
よくアニメーションを創って、その空間に投影し返して
sort of to create an installation.
インスタレーションのような物をつくる
I guess, I don't know why I draw that image like that. I think it was more
思うに、なぜ私がそんな風に描くのか、 私にもわからないのよ
'cause I draw triangles a lot. And so it was like, it made sense.
私は三角形をたくさん描く そしてそれはなんというか、意味が分かるの
But it does look like some sort of computer built graphic model, doesn't it?
だけど、やっぱりコンピュータで描いたみたいな グラフィックになっているでしょう？
I look at, a lot of the time when I'm looking for ideas and research, it's um
何度も、アイデア探しとリサーチをしているとき
All the images I'm sort of taking inspiration from are digitally produced
インスピレーションを受けるものは、 全てデジタル的につくられたものなの
whether that be animation or standard illustration.
それがアニメーションでも、一般的なイラストでも
Whereas I think I've tried to retain the hand drawn element to my work
私は自分の作品に手書きの要素を残そうと しているのにね
because it's about my physical experimentation with the drawing itself.
それは描くという行為に関しての 私の身体的な実験だから
Um, as opposed to drawing it on the computer.
コンピュータで描くという事に対抗してね
But then I always seem to lead back to  animating it
だけど私は常に、アニメーションを作る ところに戻っているようだわ
and putting it through some sort of digital	process. So it's like adding a stage on.
それでそれをある種のデジタルプロセスに通す なんというか、ステージを一つを足すという感じ
And especially when producing the animations it's like a drawing and then
特にアニメーションを作っているとき、 まずドローイングみたいな物を描いて、それから
I feed it back into the computer and then, so obviously
コンピュータに入れ直す
In this age where everything's so digitally produced it kind of
全てがデジタルで作られている時代に
it kind of made sense to add style to have that element to my work as well.
私の作品にもそういうスタイルを 加えたのは自然な事だったと思う
I mean, it's hard to pinpoint at what point you take inspiration from something
誰かがインスピレーションを感じるポイントを 正確に言い当てるのは難しい
Cause you're just bombarded by information constantly, I mean I, I
定期的に、情報にただ爆撃されているから、 というか、
spent a lot of time at the internet looking at blogs and art websites and
多くの時間をブログや、アート関係の ウェブサイトを見る事に費やしていて
sometimes you don't know where you've got a little snippet of inspiration from
時々、どこからインスピレーションのかけらを もらってきたのか分からなくなるでしょ
Cause you don't document everything you find cool, do you?
だってクールだと思ったものの全てを ドキュメントしてはいないでしょう？
So yeah I probably looked at some sort of computer game or something that
多分、コンピュータゲームやなにかを見て、 それが私の描くものに影響を与えたんだと思う
influenced that. I kind of like that it has kind of a digital quality even though
そんな感じで、手で描いた物であっても、 デジタルの質感の様なものをもっている
it's a hand-drawn thing. There's nothing computerized about that
全くコンピュータを使ってないのだけど
If you go stand up close to it, it's really a rough image and the triangles aren't
近づいて見たら、それは本当にラフな イメージで、そこにある三角形は
you know, proper set lines and everything.
正確にな位置に描かれた線とか そういったものではないのにね
It's obviously hand-drawn up close, but from a distance, yeah, it looks quite digital.
それは近くで見れば明らかに手描きなのよ。だけど、 ある距離からみれば、それはとてもデジタル的に見えるの